Guide to the Mark Hall Amitin/ World of Culture for the Performing Arts, Inc. Archive MSS.121
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Personal Papers
  - Subseries I: Business files, theatre companies, flyers, general correspondence
    - Amitin interview with Alexander Sitkovetsky of the rock group Autograph, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Amitin job application - NYU, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Amitin lectures and teaching, 1969- (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Amitin lectures and teaching, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Amitin press releases, reviews, articles, 1967- (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Amitin resumes, letters of reference, job applications, 1986-1990 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Amitin wedding anniversary, undated (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Angels of Light, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Kenneth Anger monograph, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Ann Arbor Film and Video Festival, July 1989. (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Annual Avant Garde Theatre Festival of New York, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Antenna Theatre, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Are You Now or Have You Ever Been - reviews, correspondence, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Arts Alliance International, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Association Quebecoise du Jeune Theatre, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Avant Garde theatre course description, undated (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Baltimore International Theatre Festival, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Karla Palotai Berg, undated (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Steven Berkoff, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617444
    - Ron Blanchette - Demystavision, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Blue Cross/ Blue Shield health insurance, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Board of Education, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Lucretia Borgia stickers, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Brooks Travel, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Brooks Travel, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Tone Brulin - Universiti Sains Malaysia, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Burbage Theatre Ensemble, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Charles Busch - reviews, playbills, articles, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Canada, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Alessandro Cassin article on Aldo Braibanti's Poor Theatre of Solitude, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Merle Joy Amitin Cenicola press release, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Centro Maschere e Strutture Gestuali, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Shami Chaikin, January 30, 1974. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Charts and graphs, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Myung-Ja Chun, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Cleveland Public Theatre, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Colleges and Universities I, 1973-1980 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Colleges and Universities II, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Colleges and Universities III, 1975-1980 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Colleges and Universities IV, 1978-1981 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Colleges and Universities V, 1975-1980 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Colleges and Universities VI, 1975-1983 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Concept East Theatre, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Copenhagen International Theatre Festival, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617451
    - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Arizona, California, Colorado, Connecticut, DC, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Brooks Travel, Frommers Travel, dance companies, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: clients, potential clients, 1986- (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Company Theatre, Celebration Mime Co., Ralph Eastman, 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: financial, legal, 1968-1998 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Florida, Georgia, Illinois, 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: France, 1976-1981 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: High Schools, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: India, 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Indiana, Massachusetts, Michigan, Minnesota, Maryland, Missouri, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: international (unsorted), 1972-1995 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: International Sea and Air Insurance, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: landlord, Town House Associates, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Montana, Nebraska, New Jersey, New Mexico, New York, Wisconsin, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: No One Here Gets Out Alive, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: North Carolina, Ohio, Oregon, Rhode Island, Vermont, Virginia, 1971-1975 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: San Francisco Mime Troupe - By Popular Demand, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Theatre companies, artists, 1977-1994 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Visions for a Changing Theatre in China, 1979-1982 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Cruise Talent, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Dance Exchange, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Dance Theatre of Harlem - letters of recommendation, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Drama Review, Feb 1975 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Dream Theatre, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Drew University advanced acting class, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Drew University teaching post, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Earthcircus/ Jordcirkus, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Electra scripts, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Europe: general correspondence, notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Fame, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617485
    - Festivals of Fools, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Festival Mondial du Theatre, Nancy, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Festival Mondial du Theatre, Nancy, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Festival Mondial du Theatre, Nancy, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Festival Mondial du Theatre, Nancy - Patra, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Festival of Fools, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Film and video list, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Film/ video rentals, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Film/ video rentals, Middlebury College, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Finland, Denmark, Sweden, U.S.S.R. tour, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Mika Fowler, November 9, 1973. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Frommer Holidays, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Andre Gintzburger, 1968-1977 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Grow Your Own Street Theater flyer, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Hauser Orkater, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Hertz Car Rental, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Bob Heuck - Shalom, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Humboldt State University - film/ video correspondence, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - "The Image of Two Cities: Paris, New York" - junior intro to visual arts …, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Insurance claims, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Inter-Collegiate Holidays Inc., 1981 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - International Movement Symposium, U.S.S.R., Apr 1990 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - International Theatre Festival, Copenhagen, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - International Theatre Institute (Martha Coigney), 1984- (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Interpacific Tours, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - In the Soup (Cacous Films), 1991 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Dan Isaac, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Robert Francis Jenkins - introduction to Ph.D. on people's theatre groups, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Job Branch Theatre, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Joffrey Ballet, Europe, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Judson - Gertrude Stein tribute, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Jury duty, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Michele Kokosowski, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Al Kraizer - The American Vaudeville Centennial, undated (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Jesse Last - Rainbow's End script, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Legal correspondence, bills, 1971-1975 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Mark Jordan Legan poems, undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Letterheads and envelopes, undated (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Limelight Editions - publication of Decoding Utopia: The History of the Living Theatre, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Joan Littlewood, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Lister International travel, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Los Angeles Mask Theatre, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Gary Lund, Ric Pease, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Lypsinka, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Madame Butterfly press, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617469
    - The Manhattan Project, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Methodist College Workshop, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Judith Miller dissertation - Theatre and Revolution Since 1968, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Arthur Miller newsletter, Nov 10, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Ted Milton, 1975- (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Movement theatre literature, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Mystic Fire video list, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - N.E.A. Guidelines for Sponsors, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - New Dramatists Luncheon, May 20, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - The New School course descriptions, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters, press (various), 1975- (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - The New Theatre Festival, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - New York University Continuing Education, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - New York University Experimental Theatre Wing, 1978- (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Nightfire, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Notes and bibliography for thesis on mysticism in the theatre, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - The NOW Agency list of speakers, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - The Open Fist Theater, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Otrabanda (Tone Brulin), 1969-1973 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Serge Ouaknine CVs, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Pasadena Playhouse, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - The Performance Group, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - The Performance Group - Rumstick Road, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Performance Studies Conference, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - The Performing Arts Journal, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - The Performing Arts Journal publications, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Personal business, 1973- (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Personal memorabilia, 1964- (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Personal notes, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Photos and resumes of clients, potential clients, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Piscator Foundation project proposal, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - "Political Theater Sprouts across U.S." - interview with Mark Amtin for Florida, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Posters, programs, flyers, playbills, undated (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Project Interplay, undated (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Pterodactyls, undated (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Radical Theatre Repertory, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617493
    - Rain Without Thunder- portion of script, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Recommended reading lists, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Quebec Festival, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Record Company Directory, July 4, 1986. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Reports on Amitin workshops, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - The Resistable Rise of Arturo Ui, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Russia - general papers and Mark Amitin's articles on Russian theatre and rock music, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Russian theatre program, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Russian tour group, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Evan Schindler case, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Richard Avi Seaver CV, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Second Summer Theatre Workshop, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Shantih: New International Writings vol 1, no 2, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Shasta College teaching, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Stuart Sherman, Oct 1992 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Smithsonian Institution Touring Performing Service brochure, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Peter Snow and Ulrika Nord, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Solaris (Henry Smith), 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Solaris Dance Theatre correspondence, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Solaris European tour, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Solaris publicity material, 1977- (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - South American tour presentation, Jan 1983 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - James Spicer memorial service, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Spoleto Festival, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Squat Theatre press, 1978-1982 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Squat Theatre publicity package, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Student travel programs, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - SUNY Stony Brook, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Terminal: A Collective Work Created by the Open Theatre Ensemble, undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Theatre arts periodicals list, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Theatre at St Clements Church, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Theatre Communications Group Touring Information Service, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Theatre Crafts Magazine, 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Theatre Festival, Wroclaw, Poland, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Theatre Festival, Wroclaw, Poland, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Travel Delegates Corporation, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - United Artists, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - U.S.S.R. tour, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Van Itallie Foundation - grant for Mark Amitin, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Susana Ventura/ Penny Arcade, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Video equipment, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Vincennes theatre piece - notes, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - "Visions for a Changing Theatre" - letters, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - "Visions for a Changing Theatre" - notes, undated (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - "Vocations for Social Change", 1972 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Warner Theatre Productions, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Wellesley College lecture, October 3, 1984. (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Wesleyan University - Theatre in China lecture, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Who's Who in America, 1986-1993 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - The Who - Tommy, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Williamstown Theatre Festival, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Workshop notes, undated (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - World Theatre Festival, Denver, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Wroclaw Festival, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Yes, Nos Temos Bananas- press, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - You Tell Me Yours and I'll Tell You Mine, undated (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Zart Kabaret/ Alan Mintz, Sense and Nonsense/ Steve Clorfeine, August 1989. (Box 33, Folder 59)
- Series II: Universal Movement Theatre Repertory
  Material in this series includes correspondence, financial records, flyers, playbills, brochures, CVs, and general business documents. Some folders contain materials spanning several years, some of which is undated.
  - American Dance Festival, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040617501
  - Mark Amitin, "The Theatre of Experiment and the Avant Garde", undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Mark Amitin workshops, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Arena Stage, 1968-1972 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Keith Berger, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Bread and Puppet Theatre, 1971- (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Bread and Puppet Theatre chap books, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Bread and Puppet Theatre flyers, playbills, 1972- (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Kenneth H. Browne résumé, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Cambridge Ensemble, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Caravan Theatre, 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Joseph Chaikin, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Circle Theatre Company, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - The Company Theatre, 1970-1973 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Wayne County, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Diane di Prima, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Ã‰cole Jacques Lecoq, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Electra- correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Electra- correspondence for tour, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Electra- flyers, programs, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Electra- legal, budgets, calendars, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Electra- press, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Electra- script, undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Electra- technical, 1972- (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Electra- travel, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - El Teatro Campesino, 1967-1976 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - El Teatro Campesino travel arrangements, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Jean Erdman submissions to UMTR, 1955- (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Festival of Indian Devotional Arts, 1971- (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Festival of Underground Theatre, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Firehouse Theater Company, undated (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Tommy Flowers press clippings, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Friends Road Show, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Friends Road Show - correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Michael Grando, 1970- (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Grants, 1970-1973 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Grupo Oficina Brasil, undated (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - William Hoffmann, undated (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Independence '76 Festival of Theatre, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040617519
  - The King's Crown and I, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Larry Kornfeld: The Theatre of Gertrude Stein, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - John Lahr, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - La Mama performances, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Le Plan K, 1975-1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Le Plan K - correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Le Plan K - flyers, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Les Treteaux Libres, 1968- (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Living Poem Theater, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Mabou Mines, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - The Making of Americans, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - The Manhattan Project, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Kres Mersky, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Arthur Mitchell proposal, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Mrs McGill sheet music, script, notes, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Meredith Monk, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Musica Elettronica Viva, 1969-1972 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - The New Cell Theatre, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - New Horizons in Theatre conference, April 1971. (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - The New Theatre, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Nuevo Teatro Pobre de America, 1969- (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - The Open Theatre, 1971-1983 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Otrabanda, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Paradise Now flyers, undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - The People Show, 1971-1979 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - The Performance Group, 1971-1975 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - The Performance Group - Mother Courage, 1970-1975 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Pilobolus, undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - The Provisional Theatre, 1972-1975 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - The Provisional Theatre - interview with Steve Kent, Candy Laughlin, Barry Opper, August 10, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Reality Theatre, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - The Ridiculous Theatrical Company, undated (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Arthur Sainer, 1976- (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Arthur Sainer - Everysam script, undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Arthur Sainer - II Piece Quiet script, undated (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - The San Francisco Mime Troupe, 1967-1982 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - The San Francisco Mime Troupe - flyers, undated (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Script (unidentified - Bill Peake?), undated (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - The Seagull reviews, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - The Shaliko Company, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - The Shaliko Company, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Shelter Program of Theatre of St Clements, undated (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Clément Simard, "Theatres USA", 1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040617527
  - Ekatrina Sobenchenskaya, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Soon 3, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Gertrude Stein's The Making of Americans, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Studio II, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Cecil Taylor press, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Theatre for the New City, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Theatre Laboratoire Vicinal, 1970-1975 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Theatre Laboratoire Vicinal, 1970-1978 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Theatre Laboratoire Vicinal - North American Tour, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Theatre Now flyers, April 23, 1975. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Theatre of Latin America, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Theatre of the Eighth Decade, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Toronto Dance Theatre, 1968-1971 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - The Two Penny Circus, undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - UMTR advertisement, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - UMTR applicants, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - UMTR board of directors, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - UMTR brochure, undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - UMTR cables and telegrams, 1972-1976 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - UMTR consultants, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - UMTR contact sheet, undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - UMTR contracts, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - UMTR contracts and related business, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - UMTR correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - UMTR correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - UMTR correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - UMTR correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - UMTR general business, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - UMTR legal documents, 1970-1976 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - UMTR original art for advertisement, undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie, A Fable, undated (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie, A Fable flyers, press, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Westbeth Playwrights' Feminist Collective, undated (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Yezidas, undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Series III: The Living Theatre
  Dates are given wherever possible but since some folders contain undated or variously dated materials, the dates listed here are not entirely accurate or do not cover the entire period indicated.
  - Abbreviations of play titles, bibliographies, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040617535
  - ABC No Rio - flyers, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Act-Up Workshop - flyers, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Address lists, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Carlo Altomarle scene study class - flyer, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - American Express funds appeal, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Mark Amitin drafts of article on The Living Theatre, 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Anarchia reviews, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - "Anarchists and the Pro-Hierarchical Left" by Judith Malina, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Jim Anderson 1929-1975 - Obituary (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Antigone- The Elders scene, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Antigone- photographs (photocopies), undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Antigone- Reed College flyer, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Antigone- reviews, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Antigone- "Sartre through Beckett", undated (Box 37, Folder 15)